Finding Aid for College of Engineering (University of Michigan) records 1860-2010
Bentley Historical Library, University of Michigan
- Dean's Files, 1904-1991
  - Ivan C. Crawford and Successors
    - Topical Files
      - Department Reviews
        - Aerospace Engineering, 1967 (Box 19)
        - Chemical and Metallurgical Engineering, 1966-1967 (Box 19)
        - Electrical Engineering, 1964-1968; 2 folders (Box 19)
        - Engineering Mechanics, 1969 (Box 19)
        - English, 1963-1966 (Box 19)
        - Industrial Engineering, 1966-1967 (Box 19)
        - Naval Architecture and Marine Engineering, 1955-157, 1964-1971; 4 folders (Box 19)
      - Development Council, 1952-1970 (Box 19)
      - Dorr, Harold M., 1956-1962 (Box 19)
      - Douglas Aircraft Company, 1962 (Box 19)
      - Edison Foundation, Inc., 1957 (Box 19)
      - Educational Policy Committee, 1953-1959 (Box 19)
      - Electric Power Systems Laboratory, 1954 (Box 19)
      - Electrical and Computer Engineering, 1970-1971; 1974-1977; 3 folders (Box 19)
      - Electrical Engineering
        - 1952-1964, 3 folders (Box 19)
        - 1964-1969, 4 folders (Box 20)
      - Electrical Engineering: Evaluation Questionnaire, 1967; 4 folders (Box 20)
      - Engineering Council, 1955-1969; 4 folders (Box 20)
      - Engineering Council, Big Ten Conference, 1968 (Box 20)
      - Engineering Mathematics Statistics Committee, 1967-1979 (Box 20)
      - Engineering Physics, 1944-1967 (Box 20)
      - Engineering Psychology, 1960 (Box 20)
      - Engineering Research, Department of
        - Advisory Board, 1920 (Box 20)
        - Annual Reports, 1927-1929 (Box 20)
        - Executive Committee, 1920 (Box 20)
        - Operating Statement, 1920-1925 (Box 20)
      - Engineering Research Institute
        - 1939-1958, 2 folders (Box 20)
        - Correspondence
          - 1948-1952 (Box 20)
          - 1953-1958, 5 folders (Box 21)
        - Financial Statements, 1956-1958; 2 folders (Box 21)
      - Engineers' Wives, Society of, 1954-1956 (Box 21)
      - Enrollment, 1956-1971; 2 folders (Box 21)
      - Equipment, 1970-1976 (Box 21)
      - Esso Company, 1955 (Box 21)
      - Executive Committee, 1957-1977; 2 folders (Box 21)
      - Faculty, 1963-1974; 2 folders (Box 21)
      - Faculty Compensation for Outside Research, 1959-1963; 3 folders (Box 21)
      - Faculty Dinner, 1968-1972 (Box 21)
      - Faculty Meeting Agendas, 1967-1971; 2 folders (Box 21)
      - Fellowship Program, 1960-1966 (Box 22)
      - Fluids and Automotive Laboratory Renovation Proposal, 1969 (Box 22)
      - Ford Faculty Development, 1959-1968; 2 folders (Box 22)
      - General Motors, 1952-1969 (Box 22)
      - Gifts Reported
        - 1876-1930 (Box 22)
        - 1951-1955 (Box 22)
        - 1956-1959 (Box 22)
        - 1970-1971 (Box 22)
      - Graduate School, 1954-1976; 5 folders (Box 22)
      - Greater Ann Arbor Research Park, 1958-1962 (Box 22)
      - Greater Ann Arbor Research Park-University Coordinating Committee, 1961-1963 (Box 22)
      - Hatcher, Harlan H., 1952-1969 (Box 22)
      - Highway Laboratory, 1934-1936; 1955-1969; 3 folders (Box 22)
      - Highway Laboratory, Abstracts of Correspondence, 1967-1969 (Box 22)
      - Honors and Awards, 1960-1968 (Box 22)
      - Honors Convocation, 1961 (Box 22)
      - Honors Luncheon, 1967-1971 (Box 22)
      - Humanities, 1961-1967 (Box 22)
      - M-Miscellaneous, 1953-1968 (Box 23)
      - Manual for the Teaching of Industrial Law, 1952 (Box 23)
      - Materials Engineering, 1951-1969 (Box 23)
      - Mathematics, 1961-1969 (Box 23)
      - Mechanical and Industrial Engineering, 1953-1956 (Box 23)
      - Mechanical Engineering
        - 1956-1969, 1972-1977; 4 folders (Box 23)
        - Centennial, 1968 (Box 23)
        - Chairmanship, 1955-1958 (Box 23)
      - Merker, Harvey M., 1952-1956 (Box 23)
      - Mesrobian, Robert B., 1951-1952 (Box 23)
      - Meteorology and Oceanography, Department of, 1962-1968 (Box 23)
      - Mexican Highway Contract, 1954 (Box 23)
      - Michigan Technic, 1933; 1945-1947 (Box 23)
      - Minority Projects, 1978 (Box 23)
      - Minority Report, 1977 (Box 23)
      - Name and School Committee, 1964-1966 (Box 23)
      - NASA Proposals, 1967 (Box 23)
      - Naval Architecture, 1963-1971 (Box 23)
      - Naval Architecture and Marine Engineering, 1952-1962 (Box 23)
      - Newspaper Clippings, 1953-1955 (Box 23)
      - Nuclear Energy Laboratory Building, 1963 (Box 23)
      - Nuclear Engineering
        - 1949-1967 (Box 24)
        - Committee, 1949-1958 (Box 24)
        - Program, 1957-1958 (Box 24)
      - Nuclear Reactor
        - Description and Operation, Ford Nuclear Reactor, 1957 (Box 24)
        - Operations Summary, Ford Nuclear Reactor, 1966-1967 (Box 24)
        - Proposal to Build, 1952 (Box 24)
      - Parker, James W., 1953-1958 (Box 24)
      - Placement, 1952-1961 (Box 24)
      - Planning Committee of University, 1965-1969 (Box 24)
      - Planning Conference, 1967 (Box 24)
      - Plans and Projections, 1968 (Box 24)
      - Plant Department, 1954 (Box 24)
      - Plasma Dynamics Laboratory, 1968 (Box 24)
      - Plasma Research, 1959-1961 (Box 24)
      - Potential Conflict of Interest Reports, 1966-67 (Box 24)
      - Prine, Arthur D., 1952-1956 (Box 24)
      - Production Engineering, 1951-1956 (Box 24)
      - Project Michigan, 1954-1959; 3 folders (Box 24)
      - Project Themis Proposal, 1967 (Box 24)
      - Radio Astronomy, 1959-1961 (Box 24)
      - Recruiting of Students by Industry, 1967-1968 (Box 24)
      - ROTC, 1948 (Box 24)
      - S-Miscellaneous, 1934-1967 (scattered) (Box 24)
      - Scholastic Standing Committee, 1952-1976 (Box 24)
      - SCORE-"Students' Competition on Relevant Engineering,", 1971-1973 (Box 24)
      - Sea Grant, 1971-1973 (Box 24)
      - Sesquicentennial
        - 1963-1967 (Box 24)
        - Award Recipients, 1966-1967 (Box 25)
        - Honorary Degree Recipients, 1967 (Box 25)
        - News Releases, 1967 (Box 25)
      - Symposium on Solid and Fluid Mechanics, 1967 (Box 25)
      - Sigma Rho Tau, 1930-1955 (scattered) (Box 25)
      - Speeches and Articles
        - Dean Attwood, 1957-1965; 2 folders (Box 25)
        - Dean Van Wylen, 1961-1971; undated; 6 folders (Box 25)
      - Standing Committee, 1934-1969 (scattered) (Box 25)
      - Steinman, David B., 1953-1955; 1959 (Box 25)
      - Technical University of Berlin, 1969-1973; 2 folders (Box 25)
      - Television Courses, 1950-1954 (Box 25)
      - Thermodynamics, 1956 (Box 25)
      - University of Michigan Research Institute (UMRI)
        - Correspondence, 1957-1960 (Box 25)
        - Faculty Participation, 1958-1961; 2 folders (Box 25)
      - Vice-President
        - Niehuss, Marvin L., 1951-1955 (Box 25)
        - Norman, A. G., 1960-1972 (Box 26)
        - Sawyer, Ralph A., 1959-1967 (Box 26)
        - Smith, Allan F., 1962-1968; 2 folders (Box 26)
      - Walter, Erich A., Assistant to the President, 1953-1965 (Box 26)
      - Willow Run Airport, 1947 (Box 26)
      - Willow Run Laboratories, 1952-1969 (Box 26)
      - Willow Run Research Center, 1952-1954 (Box 26)
    - Communications with Regents
      - 1955-1969, 10 folders (Box 26)
  - Charles M .Vest, 1986-1990
    The subseries Charles Vest, 1986-1990 (5.8 linear feet) is. Although the majority of the materials date from the deanships of Charles M. Vest (1986-1989) and Daniel E. Atkins (Interim Dean, 1989-1990), the records do include some earlier materials. However, the researcher should be aware that there is a gap in the DEAN'S FILES series for the years 1980-1986; no records were received in this accession for the deanships of Hansford W. Farris (Acting Dean, 1980-1981) and James J. Duderstadt (1981-1986), which are more thoroughly documented in the 1993-1996 Accessions. Also, although in previous accessions the records regarding administrative duties, faculty and staff, and students are contained in their own series, in the 1992 Accession these types of records are included within the two series Dean's Files, 1986-1990 and Senior Associate Dean's Files, 1980-1992.
    The Dean's Files, 1986-1990 series is arranged alphabetically by topic and documents the wide-ranging issues and concerns facing the college during these years. The series is notable for its wealth of information on the College of Engineering's research and development efforts in an age of increasing technology. These efforts are documented in the folders "Centers, Institutes, and Laboratories"; "Committees"; "Development"; and "Research." Much of the information in this series is of an administrative nature, such as that found in the "Administration Files" (which include "Faculty" and "Staff" files), "Awards," and "Students." The large group of folders on Departments are also concerned mostly with administrative issues, but some contain departmental reviews. (The researcher interested in trends and developments within the various departments of the college will find more information in the Departmental Files section of the Senior Associate Dean's Files, 1980-1992.) Earlier materials include information on the college's relocation in 1982 to North Campus ("North Campus") and statistics ("Administration Files; Statistics and Peer Institute Data").
    - Topical Files
      - Accreditation Board for Engineering Technology, Inc. (ABET), 1981-1989 (Box 38)
      - Administration Files
        - General, 1986-1989; 2 folders (Box 38)
        - Committee Assignments, College Representatives and Administrative Appointments, 1980-1990 (Box 38)
        - Faculty
          - Appointments, 1987 (Box 51)
            [PR RESTRICTED until July 1, 2017 ]
          - Faculty Meetings, 1988-1989 (Box 38)
          - Letters to Faculty, 1986-1990 (Box 38)
          - Professorships, 1985-1989 (Box 38)
          - Rules of the Faculty, 1983-1985; undated (Box 38)
        - Policies, 1973-1989 (Box 38)
        - Records Office, Transfer of Duties to Registrar, 1982 (Box 38)
        - Searches
          - Assistant to the Dean for Admissions and Instruction, 1989 (Box 51)
            [PR RESTRICTED until July. 1, 2019 ]
          - Assistant to the Dean for Continuing Engineering Education, 1989 (Box 51)
            [PR RESTRICTED until Jan. 1, 2019 ]
        - Staff Meetings Minutes, 1986-1989 (Box 38)
        - Statistics and Peer Institute Data, 1980-1988 (Box 38)
        - Strategic Planning Retreat, 1989 (Box 38)
      - Affirmative Action, 1986-1989 (Box 38)
      - Awards
        - General, 1986-1989; 2 folders (Box 38)
        - Michigan Society of Fellows, 1987-1989 (Box 38)
        - National Medal of Science/Technology, 1986-1989; 2 folders (Box 38)
        - Packard Fellowship, 1988 (Box 38)
        - Presidential Initiatives Fund, 1987-1988 (Box 38)
        - Undergraduate Initiatives Fund, 1986-1988; 2 folders (Box 38)
      - Centers, Institutes, and Laboratories
        - University of Michigan
          - Design Competitiveness, Center for, 1987 (Box 38)
          - Integrated Technology Instruction Center (ITIC), 1986-1989; 4 folders (Box 38)
          - Research on Integrated Manufacturing, Center for (CRIM), 1986-1988 (Box 38)
          - Science and Technology, Institute of (IST)
            - General, 1987 (Box 38)
            - Industrial Development and Special Projects Divisions (re: transfer to School of Business Administration), 1987-1989; 2 folders (Box 38)
          - Solid State Electronics Laboratory
            - General, 1983-1985 (Box 39)
            - Dedication, 1987 (Box 39)
          - Space Physics Research Laboratory, 1987 (Box 39)
        - External
          - General Motors Institute, 1987 (Box 39)
          - Industrial Technology Institute, 1986-1989 (Box 39)
          - Manufacturing Science, National Center for (NCMS), 1988 (Box 39)
          - Research and Technology, Center for(Grand Rapids), 1986; 1988 (Box 39)
      - Committees
        - College of Engineering
          - Academic Policy and Budget Group, 1987-1988 (Box 39)
          - Chairman's Advisory Committee, 1986-1989; 4 folders (Box 39)
          - Curriculum Committee, 1986-1988 (Box 39)
          - Engineering Math-Statistics-Physics Committee, 1986-1987 (Box 39)
          - Executive Committee (College of Engineering)
            - 1981 (Box 39)
            - 1986-1989 (Box 39)
          - Instructional Programs and Policies Group (IPPG), 1988 (Box 39)
          - National Advisory Committee, 1984-1989; 6 folders (Box 39)
          - Primary Research Committee, Ad Hoc, 1980-1982 (Box 39)
          - Research Programs and Policies Group, 1987-1988 (Box 39)
          - Robotics Research Oversight Committee, 1989 (Box 39)
        - University of Michigan
          - Academic Affairs Advisory Council, 1988-1989 (Box 39)
          - Senate Advisory Committee on University Affairs (SACUA), 1986-1987 (Box 39)
        - External
          - Big Ten Plus Engineering Deans, 1982-1989; 3 folders (Box 40)
          - Michigan Engineering Deans Council, 1987-1989; 7 folders (Box 40)
      - Community Colleges, 1988 (Box 40)
      - Curriculum and Courses
        - General, 1988-1989 (Box 40)
        - Applied Physics Program, 1983-1990 (Box 40)
        - Engineering 103, 1988 (Box 40)
        - Engineering 303, 1987-1988 (Box 40)
        - Humanities and Social Science Component, 1986-1988 (Box 40)
        - Technical Communications Program, 1988 (Box 40)
        - Urban, Technological and Environmental Planning (UTEP) Interdisciplinary Program, Review, 1987 (Box 40)
      - Departments
        - Aerospace Engineering
          - General, 1986-1988 (Box 40)
          - Reviews, 1982; 1987-1988 (Box 40)
        - Atmospheric, Oceanic, and Space Sciences
          - General, 1986-1989 (Box 40)
          - Oceanography Transfer, 1986-1987 (Box 51)
            [PR RESTRICTED until Jan. 1, 2017 ]
          - Promotions, Tenure, and Reappointments, 1986-1988 (Box 51)
            [PR RESTRICTED until Jan. 1, 2018 ]
          - Retirements, 1986 (Box 51)
          - Review, 1985 (Box 40)
        - Chemical Engineering
          - General, 1986-1988 (Box 40)
          - Visitation Committee, 1987 (Box 40)
        - Civil Engineering
          - General, 1986-1989 (Box 40)
          - Promotions, Tenure, and Reappointments, 1986; 1989 (Box 51)
          - Review, 1988 (Box 40)
        - Electrical Engineering and Computer Science
          - General, 1986-1989; 5 folders (Box 40)
          - Appointments, 1986 (Box 51)
          - Chairman Search, 1986-1987 (Box 51)
          - Review, 1985 (Box 40)
        - Industrial and Operations Engineering
          - General, 1986-1989 (Box 40)
          - Dual Degree Program with School of Business Administration, 1985-1986 (Box 40)
          - Ergonomics, Center for, 1986-1989 (Box 40)
          - Occupational Health and Safety Engineering, Center for, 1988-1989 (Box 40)
        - Materials Science and Engineering, 1986-1989 (Box 40)
        - Materials and Metallurgical Engineering
          - Review, Internal, 1983 (Box 40)
        - Mechanical Engineering and Applied Mechanics
          - General, 1986-1989; 2 folders (Box 41)
          - Promotions, Tenure, and Reappointments, 1987 (Box 51)
          - Recruitment, 1987-1988 (Box 41)
          - Retirement, 1988 (Box 41)
          - Reviews, Internal
            - 1978, 1982 (Box 41)
            - 1987, 3 folders (Box 41)
            - 1990 (Box 41)
        - Naval Architecture and Marine Engineering
          - General, 1986-1989 (Box 41)
          - Department Name Change, 1987 (Box 41)
          - Recruitment, 1987 (Box 51)
            [SR RESTRICTED until Jan. 1, 2062 ]
        - Nuclear Engineering
          - Michigan Memorial Phoenix Project
            - General, 1987-1989 (Box 41)
            - Director Search, 1986-1988 (Box 51)
      - Development
        - General
          - Aerospace Complex and Planning, 1986-1989; 3 folders (Box 41)
          - Emeritus Weekend, 1989 (Box 41)
          - Engineering Alumni Governing Board, 1986-1988 (Box 41)
          - Japan, 1989 (Box 41)
          - Partners in Leadership, 1989 (Box 41)
        - Bequests, Endowments, and Gifts
          - Donald L. Katz Fund, 1989 (Box 41)
          - F-X Bagnoud Association, 1989-1990 (Box 41)
          - Jonathan Laitone Memorial Fund, 1987 (Box 41)
          - Miller, Otto N., 1987-1988 (Box 41)
        - Bequests, Endowments, and Gifts, cont
          - Roger M. Jones Memorial Fund, 1987-1989 (Box 41)
          - Shannon, Claude E., 1987-1988 (Box 41)
          - Smith, Goff, 1986-1988 (Box 41)
          - Wheeler, Malcolm D., 1989 (Box 41)
          - Wiesner, Jerome, 1986-1988 (Box 41)
        - Corporate
          - Booth Newspapers, 1988 (Box 41)
          - Chrysler Corporation, 1986; 1988; 2 folders (Box 41)
          - Digital Equipment Corporation, 1986; 1989; 2 folders (Box 41)
          - Ford Motor Company
            - General, 1987-1989 (Box 41)
            - Joint Projects, 1989 (Box 41)
            - Visits by Ford, 1987-1988 (Box 41)
          - Gehrung Associates University Relations Counselors, Inc., 1986-1988 (Box 41)
          - General Electric, 1986-1990 (Box 41)
          - General Instrument Corporation, 1986 (Box 41)
          - General Motors Corporation
            - General, 1987-1989 (Box 41)
            - Proposal, 1988 (Box 41)
            - Prospectus, 1981 (Box 41)
            - Visits by and Trips to GM, 1987-1989; 6 folders (Box 41)
          - Honda, 1988 (Box 41)
          - Honeywell, 1988 (Box 41)
          - International Business Machines Corporation (IBM)
            - General, 1986-1989 (Box 42)
            - Proposals, 1988-1989; 2 folders (Box 42)
            - Visits by and Trips to IBM, 1986-1988; 3 folders (Box 42)
          - Kellogg Foundation, 1987 (Box 42)
          - McDonnell Douglas Foundation, 1986-1989 (Box 42)
          - Monroe-Brown Foundation, 1987-1989 (Box 42)
          - Monsanto Company, 1988 (Box 42)
          - Mott (Charles Stewart) Foundation, 1988 (Box 42)
          - Newport Corporation, 1985-1987 (Box 42)
          - Northern Telecom, Inc., 1986-1989 (Box 42)
          - SEMATECH, 1987 (Box 42)
          - Sinclair and Rush, Inc., 1988 (Box 42)
          - Smiths Industries, 1989 (Box 42)
          - Software Engineering Institute, 1986 (Box 42)
          - Tera Computer Company, 1988 (Box 42)
          - Townsend and Bottum, Inc., 1987 (Box 42)
          - Unisys Corporation, 1987-1989 (Box 42)
          - Westinghouse Corporation, 1986-1991 (Box 42)
          - Whirlpool Corporation, 1987-1989 (Box 42)
          - Xerox Corporation, 1986; 1989 (Box 42)
        - Trips by and Visits to College of Engineering
          - General, 1986-1989 (Box 42)
          - California
            - General, 1986-1987; 1989; 2 folders (Box 42)
            - Los Angeles, 1988 (Box 42)
          - Grand Rapids, 1986; 2 folders (Box 42)
          - Minnesota (Visit by Minn. Governor Perpich), 1987 (Box 42)
          - New York, 1986; 1989 (Box 42)
          - Seattle and San Francisco, 1986 (Box 42)
          - Texas, 1989 (Box 42)
      - Foreign Citizens as Engineers in the United States, 1988 (Box 42)
      - Government
        - Federal
          - General, 1985-1989 (Box 42)
          - Heebink, David, 1987-1989 (Box 42)
          - Trips to Washington, D.C., 1987-1988 (Box 42)
          - Visits to UM by Federal Officials,1986, 1988 (Box 42)
        - State
          - General, 1983-1989 (Box 42)
          - Budget Request to State from College for, 1985/86; 1985 (Box 42)
          - Capital Outlay Appropriation Analysis, 1988 (Box 42)
          - "The Crisis Facing Engineering Education in Michigan; A Call For Action,", 1985 (Box 42)
          - Engineering Bill 104, 1987 (Box 42)
          - Government Day, 1987 (Box 42)
          - Mackinaw Island Legislative Conference, 1987 (Box 42)
          - "A Unique Opportunity For Michigan's Future: an Investment in Engineering Excellence,", 1985 (Box 42)
          - Visits to UM by State Officials, 1986-1988 (Box 42)
      - Human Capital (includes Michigan's Technical Human Resource Needs meeting materials), 1988-1989 (Box 42)
      - North Campus
        - College of Engineering Move to North Campus, 1982 (Box 42)
        - North Campus Commons, 1986; 1989 (Box 42)
      - Research
        - Electro-rheological Fluids, 1987-1989 (Box 43)
        - Engineering Research Center
          - General, 1986-1991 (Box 43)
          - Proposals
            - Next Generation Quality Control in Manufacturing, 1989 (Box 43)
            - Unified and Accelerated Methods of Automotive Design, 1989; 2 folders (Box 43)
        - Experimental Research in Electronic Submission (EXPRES), 1986-1988 (Box 43)
        - Intellectual Property, 1986-1987 (Box 43)
        - Interdisciplinary Research, 1986 (Box 43)
        - Major Coordinated Research Initiatives, Summary of, 1984 (Box 43)
        - National Science Foundation
          - Collaboration Science and Technology, Center for, 1987-1989; 2 folders (Box 43)
          - Forum on Engineering Education, 1987 (Box 43)
          - Visits to UM, 1987; 2 folders (Box 43)
        - Nursing School of (regarding proposal for Nursing Satellite Telecommunications Planning Project), 1988 (Box 43)
        - Opposition to Research, 1986 (Box 43)
        - Research Excellence Fund, 1985-1989; 2 folders (Box 43)
        - Research Retreats, 1988-1989 (Box 43)
        - Superconducting Super Collider (site visit), 1988 (Box 43)
      - Students
        - General, 1987-1989 (Box 43)
        - Admissions
          - General, 1989 (Box 43)
          - Preferred Admissions Program, 1985-1986 (Box 43)
        - Graduate Students
          - Graduate Student Assistants (GSAs)
            - Policies and Issues, 1987-1988 (Box 43)
            - Tax Issues, 1988 (Box 43)
            - Tuition and Support, 1987-1989 (Box 43)
          - Minority Graduate Students, 1988-1989 (Box 43)
        - Student Exchange Programs, 1986-1989 (Box 43)
        - Student Publications, 1987 (Box 43)
  - Deans Office Files, circa 1945-1990
    The Dean's Office Files series is a continuation from previous accessions. It spans the years 1945-1991, although it primarily documents the period 1950 to 1990. The material includes correspondence, memoranda, reports and budgets, and tends to be administrative rather than personal records. The Dean's Office Files have been divided into two sub-subseries: Deans' Administrative Files and Deans' Departmental Files.
    - Deans' Administrative Files
      The Deans' Administrative Files (3.5 linear feet) overlap chronologically with sections of earlier accessions, but provide more detailed documentation of program development, cooperative programs with private industry, experiments with instructional television, and the long-term planning which was required for the move to North Campus. This subseries is strongest for the years from the mid-1950s to mid-1980s.
      - Accreditation Data, 1959 (Box 52)
      - Affirmative Action Statistics, 1972-1973 (Box 52)
      - Annual Fund Letters, 1967-1978; 1987; 2 folders (Box 52)
      - Annual Fund Report and History, 1990 (Box 52)
      - Annual Fund Coordinating Council, 1976-1977 (Box 52)
      - Commission on Undergraduate Engineering Education, 1985-1988 (Box 52)
      - Committee on Information Storage and Retrieval, 1966-1968 (Box 52)
      - Correspondence "R", 1953-1977
        - 1953-1977 (Box 52)
        - 1956-1957 (Box 84)
          [SR RESTRICTED until Jan. 1, 2031 ]
      - Engineering Open Houses, 1938-1955 (Box 52)
      - Engineering Research Institute North Campus Building Program First Unit, 1955 (Box 52)
      - Faculty Requirement for Materials, Metallurgy and Structures Laboratory, 1958 (Box 52)
      - Improvement of Teaching Committee, 1958-1967 (Box 52)